宾夕法尼亚州  彼得・罗素议员
打扰了
Hey. Excuse me.
我是保罗・凯普拉  来见克里斯蒂娜
I'm Paul Capra. I'm here to see Christina.
这边请  凯普拉先生  她正在等你
Oh, right this way, Mr. Capra. She's expecting you.
-保罗  你好  -克里斯蒂娜
- Paul. Hi. - Hey, Christina.
-真高兴见到你  -我也是
- It's good to see you. - Yeah, you too.
吃点什么吗
Can I get you anything?
不用了  我在路上随便吃了点早饭
Nah. I grabbed some breakfast on the way down.
-那好  请坐吧  -好的  谢谢
- Okay. Have a seat. - All right. Thank you.
我请你来
I asked you down here
是因为我跟民主党议会竞选委员会
because I spoke to D triple C
和全国委员会讨论过了
and the D.N.C.
我们希望你来竞选彼得的职位
We'd like you to run for Peter's seat.
你或许知道
As you probably know,
竞选将在二月的第一周举行
the election's been set for the first week of February.
你们想让我参选
You want me to run?
你在社区的名望很高
With your stature in the community,
又有基层的组织经验
your grass roots organizing experience...
克里斯蒂娜  等等
Christina, hold on.
我知道这事很重大
I know it's a lot to consider.
这才一个月
It's only been a month.
我们还得继续执政  保罗
Well, we still have to govern, Paul.
我以为你叫我来
I thought you asked me down here
是要跟我聊聊之类的
because you wanted to talk or something.
是啊  聊竞选的事
I do. About the election.
我是说聊彼得的事
I mean about Peter.
你怎么没来参加葬礼
How come you didn't go to the funeral?
我做不到
I couldn't.
你最近怎么样
How you been holding up?
我还好  维持机关正常运转不太容易
I'm all right. It's been hard keeping the office on track.
上帝啊  去他的机关
Jesus. Screw the office.
你自己还好吗
What about you?
你不用硬撑着  克里斯蒂娜
You're allowed to grieve, Christina.
保罗
Paul...
有60万人指望着我们呢
there are 600,000 people counting on us.
我不能因为个人感情影响工作
I can't let my feelings get in the way of that.
可以听我把竞选的事说完了吗
Will you hear me out about running for Peter's seat?
你的审查结果相当不错
Well, you've passed the vetting process with flying colors.
-还有什么要补充的吗  -没有  先生
- Is there anything we might have missed? - No, sir.
跟我讲讲
Tell me about your
你担任监督改革委员会主席的经历吧
experience as the chair of the oversight reform committee.
我获益良多
It's been very rewarding.
你遇到的最严峻的挑战是什么
What are the biggest challenges you've had to face?
党派斗争
Partisanship.
美国众议院有435个席位
监管435个自大狂
Well, I suppose a room filled with 435 big egos
肯定不是件容易的事
isn't the most hospitable place for oversight.
你想不想成为副总统  塔比瑟
Do you want to be Vice President, Tabitha?
那将是无上荣幸  先生
It would be a great honor, sir.
我们会再联系你
We'll be in touch.
就这样吗
That's all?
-先这样吧  -谢谢您  总统先生
- For the time being. - Thank you, Mr. President.
我们得划掉她
We have to cross her off.
同意  她能把瘾君子讲睡着
I agree. She could put a crack addict to sleep.
那她怎么会出现在这张名单上
Then what is she doing on the goddamn list?
塔比瑟是位很有才干的立法者
Tabitha's a very gifted legislator.
我不需要那些理论上可行的人
I don't want people who make sense on paper.
起码给我一个可选的人
I need at least one viable option.
列这张名单的人是你们
The two of you created this list and
把名字一个个划掉的也是你们
have proceeded to cross off every name you've put on it.
这只是初次筛选  先生
It's just a first pass, sir.
我们还需要时间去审查所有...
We need time to fully vet all...
吉姆肯定会拿下宾州州长
Jim is gonna win this thing in Pennsylvania,
而我们在继任者提名问题上
and we're no closer to naming his replacement
却原地踏步了一个月
than we were a month ago.
我们会再尽力找找
Let us take another crack at it
再找几个值得考虑的人
and give you a few more names to consider.
我只需要一个让人满意的
I just want one name.
我们会在明早前答复您
We'll have something for you by tomorrow morning.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
他现在什么都会同意的
He's ready to say yes to anything.
想成功的话  我觉得你最好别在场
Yeah, for this to work, I don't think you can be there.
-起码我最初提出的时候别在  -同意
- Not when I first mention it. - I agree.
你明早报告时提出来
You bring it up in your morning brief,
我到的时候  再故作惊讶
and when I show up, I'll act surprised.
如果他愿意考虑...
Assuming he's open to the idea...
明天我们只要给他灌输这个想法就行
Look, all we have to do tomorrow is plant the notion in his head.
你肯定能说服他的
I'm sure you'll be persuasive.
-喂  -凯普拉先生吗
- Hello? - Mr. Capra?
是我  你是谁
Yeah. Who's this?
我是头条网的简宁・斯克斯基
Janine Skorsky from Slugline.
我报道罗素议员去世时曾采访过你
We spoke when I wrote the piece about Congressman Russo's passing.
我不会再接受关于彼得的采访了
I'm done giving interviews about Peter, okay?
他有很多困扰  就这样
He was a troubled guy. End of story.
我不是要问他去世的事
This is not about his death.
我打电话是因为
I'm calling you because
有来自民主党议会竞选委员会的消息称
my sources at the D Triple C are telling me
你会竞选他的职位
that you might be running for his seat.
这事我不予回答
I'm not talking about that.
但你今早确实跟
But you did have a meeting
克里斯蒂娜・盖拉格见过面了吧
this morning with Christina Gallagher, correct?
我在开车  真的不能多聊
I'm driving right now. I really shouldn't be on the phone.
如果你确实要参选  我想知道
If you do run, I would like to know
你在关闭费城船厂一事中
about your involvement in the closing of
扮演了怎样的角色
the Philadelphia shipyard.
那是华盛顿的决定
That decision was made in Washington.
没有询问协会的意见
The association wasn't consulted.
抱歉  这我很难相信
Forgive me. I find that hard to believe.
我读过所有军事基地整合委员会的笔录
I read all of the transcripts from the BRAC Commission.
罗素议员没有给出任何证词
Congressman Russo didn't give any testimony.
那你的意思是
So are you saying that
他没和你们商讨就...
he didn't consult with you once before you...
是别人逼他的  好吗  政治手段
Somebody was strong-arming him, okay? It was politics.
你知道是谁给他施的压吗
Do you know who would've pressured him?
不知道  他说是位高权重的人
Look, I don't know. He just said people up the food chain.
他有具体说明...
Did he say anything more specific about...
车太多了  我得挂了
You know what? There's traffic. I gotta go.
凯普拉先生  我想...
Mr. Capra, I would...
我要准备应对媒体吗
Should I be prepared to do press?
如果他听劝的话
If he's amenable.
你觉得我们的胜算多大
What do you think our chances are?
非要说的话  超过一半吧
Better than 50-50, if I had to say.
马修斯胜选前我们不会宣布的
We won't announce until after Matthews wins, though.
我不想承认  但我很紧张
I hate to admit it, but I'm nervous.
我也是
So am I.
只是上次我们遇到这种情况...
It's just the last time, we found ourselves...
我也是怕这个
That's my fear too.
好吧  不论怎样  打给我
All right. You call me, either way.
九个小时内给你电话
In no more than nine hours.
琳达在里面太久了
Linda's been in there far too long.
如果说服总统要这么久
If the President takes this much convincing,
那绝不是好事  我感觉得到
it doesn't bode well. I can feel it...
门那边他的犹豫
his hesitation on the other side of that door.
虽说知道结果前
I know it's pointless to worry
急也没有用
until I know what cards I'm holding.
或许他是被什么打断...
Perhaps he just got interrupted by some...
他想任命雷蒙德・塔斯克
He wants to tap Raymond Tusk.
-什么  -他觉得这想法很大胆
- What? - He thinks it's a bold idea.
是愚蠢才对  他从没任过公职
It's an idiotic idea. The man's never held public office.
这是总统喜欢他的地方之一
That's one of the things the President said he likes about him.
总统想在经济萧条时
The President wants to nominate
任命一个亿万富翁吗
a multibillionaire in a struggling economy?
半个国家都会与他对立
He'll alienate half the country.
这正是我说的
Which is exactly what I said,
但他说得很清楚
but he made it very clear
他不想让我和他争辩
he does not want me to fight him on this.
-那你根本没说到我  -都没有机会
- So you didn't mention me at all? - I never had the chance.
我能插话前他就决定好了
His mind was made up before I could say a word.
我们得让他改变主意
Well, we have to unmake it.
你可以试试  但如果你说什么
Well, you can try, but if you do,
我猜他只会干脆不许你再插手
my guess is he's gonna cut you out of the process altogether.
他看起来非常坚定
He seemed adamant.
我们该进去了
We should go in there.
-总统先生  -早上好  弗兰克
- Mr. President. - Morning, Frank.
能让我们单独谈一会儿吗  琳达
Will you give us a few minutes, Linda?
当然
Of course.
琳达告诉你了吗
Linda fill you in?
我觉得雷蒙德・塔斯克
I think Raymond Tusk
是个大胆  新奇的选择
is an exciting, bold idea.
很高兴你赞同我  琳达可不这么想
Well, I'm glad you agree. Linda didn't think so.
他是有实力的商人  聪明  但很踏实
He's a proven businessman. Brilliant, but down-to-earth.
你和他有私交吗
Do you know him personally?
我们在一次募捐会上有点头之交
I met him briefly once at a fund-raiser.
昨晚打给他时
Last night when I called him
我们才第一次深谈
was the first time we had a meaningful conversation.
他愿意考虑吗
Did he seem open to the idea?
我感觉他很不情愿
I sensed a good deal of reluctance.
他要几天时间来想想
He wanted a few days to consider.
很好  这样就有时间审查他了
Well, good. That gives us time to start vetting him.
他没问题  我去年就审查过他
He's clean. I had him vetted last year
当时想任命他为财政部长
when I was considering him for Secretary of the Treasury.
他有说为什么不情愿吗
And did he say why he's reluctant?
没说原因  只说要好好想想
No. Didn't give a reason. Just wanted to mull it over.
我想派人去圣路易斯和他当面谈
I want to send someone to St. Louis to speak to him in person,
让他接受任命
convince him to accept the nomination.
你有合适人选吗
And who are you thinking about?
我想叫琳达  但她这边工作太忙了
I'd send Linda, but there's so much work for her to do here,
而且她有时说话比较难听
and, well, she can be abrasive at times.
是啊  她是比较强势
Yeah, she can be a bit tough.
我要找个比较庄重的
I want someone with gravitas.
博奇可以考虑
Birch is a possibility,
但他并不总是站在我们这边
but he's not always been our strongest ally.
我看这种事不能托付给鲍勃
I'm not sure I would trust Bob with something like this.
我很乐意去  先生
I would be happy to go myself, sir.
我会耐心规劝  给他应得的尊重
I can use a light touch and give him the respect he deserves.
很好  我会通知他的手下你要过去
Good. I'll let his people know you're coming.
-谢谢您  总统先生  -谢谢你  弗兰克
- Thank you, Mr. President. - Thank you, Frank.
说吧  弗兰西斯
Tell me, Francis.
幸好我们做了周全的准备
It's good we were prepared for anything.
我今晚得飞去圣路易斯
I have to fly to St. Louis tonight.
"是别人逼他的"
"Somebody was strong-arming him."
我问他是谁时  他原话是
and when I asked him who, he said, quote,
-"位高权重的人"  -这可是华盛顿
- "People up the food chain." - It's Washington.
议员受到逼迫是常事
Congressmen get strong-armed all the time.
我觉得是弗兰克・安德伍德
My gut says it was Frank Underwood.
在造船厂倒闭前  他和罗素没任何往来
He had nothing to do with Russo before the shipyard closing,
然后突然就支持他了
and then suddenly he's propping him up?
那不意味着他...
That doesn't mean he was...
我们别再兜圈子了  佐伊
Let's cut the bullshit once and for all, Zoe.
我知道是他给你提供信息
I know he's been feeding you your stories.
我不想害你
I don't want to screw you over,
但我会继续深入调查
but I'm not gonna stop digging on this.
我不会承认他是我的联络人
I won't say he was a source.
但你们确实认识
But you do know each other.
给我看你的笔记  我去和他谈
Show me your notes, and I'll talk to him.
这是和凯普拉通话的笔记
These are the notes from the Capra call.
这是军事基地整合委员会听证会的笔录
And these are the transcripts from the BRAC hearing.
他们讨论到费城造船厂时
When they got to the Philadelphia shipyard,
罗素什么都没说
Russo doesn't say anything.
没关系
That's fine.
我会把两个都拖进那个文件夹里
Yeah, I would just put both of them in that file.
克莱尔  我刚接到桑科公关部的电话
Claire, I just got a call from the P.R. office at Sancorp
他们想派摄制组来
saying they wanted to send a film crew
拍我们在博茨瓦纳的滤水项目
to take footage of our filtration project in Botswana.
对  他们要用它做宣传片
Right. They're just using that for promotional material.
桑科反对我们的流域法案
Sancorp fought us on the watershed bill.
他们帮我们把滤水器运出了南苏丹
They helped us get the filters out of South Sudan.
那不是国务院做的吗
I thought that was the State Department.
不  你记得雷米・丹顿吗
No. You remember Remy Danton?
你刚来这里工作时曾在办公室见过他
You met him in your office right after you started working here.
-那个说客  -我找他帮的忙
- The lobbyist. - I asked him for his help.
现在只是投桃报李  就这样
We're just returning the favor, that's all.
克莱尔  他们的立场和我们完全相反
Claire, they're against everything we stand for.
没关系的  他们会把影片
It's harmless. They'll send the video
发给几个投资者  做些宣传
to a few of their investors and make some commercials.
这让我很不舒服
This makes me very uncomfortable... the idea...
他们会派摄制组来  吉莉安
They are sending the film crew, Gillian,
请好好配合他们
so please work with them on that.
我的同事在调查彼得・罗素
One of my colleagues is looking into Peter Russo.
认为他关闭造船厂是受你所迫
The assumption is you strong-armed him into closing the shipyard.
你同事从哪得来的消息
Where does your colleague get their information?
我不知道
I don't know.
国防部预算的分配一直是自由竞争
Allocating the D.O.D. budget is always a free-for-all.
你对他施过压吗
Did you pressure him?
船厂早日关闭
There were certain people that were gonna benefit
确实对某些人有好处
from the base closing sooner rather than later.
我没有逼迫彼得
I didn't strong-arm Peter.
我只是建议他化腐朽为优势
I advised him to trade in a losing hand for a winning one.
他得到什么优势了
How did he stand to win?
化敌为友
He made allies out of enemies.
这在国会非常可贵
That's a very valuable thing in Congress.
真希望我能给你更有料的信息
I wish I could give you something juicier,
但造船厂的关闭只是寻常的政治手腕
but the shipyard closing was just politics as usual.
我猜那个同事是斯克斯基女士
I assume your colleague is Ms. Skorsky.
她知道我们的关系吗
Does she know we're talking?
当然不知道
No. Of course not.
保持联络
Be in touch.
雷蒙德・艾伦・塔斯克的全部资料
More than you ever wanted to know about Raymond Alan Tusk...
他掌控的公司  政治贡献
the companies he controls, political contributions.
《绅士季刊》的文章  《乡野亿万富翁》
A GQ article entitled "Backwoods billionaire"
-说的是他在中西部的低调生活  -老天
- is about his humble midwestern lifestyle. - Jesus.
还有一份财务状况的披露要求
There's also a copy of the financial disclosure requirements
和保密委托的细节
and details of the blind trust.
我觉得你该从委托入手
I think the trust is where you want to focus.
这会是琳达的主意吗
Could Linda be behind all this?
什么目的
To what end?
调你出城几天
To get you out of town for a few days
只剩他们俩继续找人选
while they continue the search without your interference.
总统没理由不信任我
The President has no reason to mistrust me.
除非琳达告诉他你想当副总统
Unless Linda told him you want the Vice Presidency.
不  她陷得太深了
No. She's in way too deep.
国务卿提名的事我们就失误了
We misjudged her on the Secretary of State nomination.
那不一样  那次是攻我不备
That was different. She blindsided me.
现在她知道我眼观六路呢
Now she knows my eyes are wide open.
您要私人行装还是商务行头
Do you want the Gaffney bag or regular business?
商务行头  塔斯克愿穿便服是他的事
Regular business. Tusk can dress down if he wants to,
但我代表的是白宫
but I'm representing the White House.
让沃尔特・道尔查塔斯克
Oh, and get Walter Doyle onto Tusk.
看看能挖到什么料
Let's see if we can dig up anything.
我这就打给他
I'll call him right now.
我离开这段时间留意简宁・斯克斯基
And keep your eye on Janine Skorsky while I'm away.
她在打听罗素的事
She's been prying into Russo.
她知道什么
What does she know?
她的问题切中要害
She knows the right questions to ask.
要确保她得不到正确答案
I want to make sure she doesn't get the right answers.
我知道了
I'm on it.
麦喀顿
McCuddin.
你说什么
What was that?
麦喀顿空军基地
McCuddin Air Force Base.
军事基地整合委员会于4月12日举行听证
BRAC hearing. Was there on April 12th.
不到一周后大卫・拉斯姆森离职
David Rasmussen stepped down less than a week later.
乌麦克接替了他  很可能...
Womack takes his place. So maybe...
等下  慢点
Wait. Slow down.
麦喀顿在他的选区
McCudden is in his district.
是造船厂那事吗
Is that the shipyard thing?
简宁  给我回电
Janine, call me back.
我想是乌麦克给罗素施了压
I think it was Womack who pressured Russo.
罗素可能只是想卖个人情
Russo was probably just earning a favor
回头再找回来
he could cash in later.
我随时都在
I'm around.
你有没有为阻止她报道而跟她争过
Did you ever have to fight her to kill a story?
简宁吗
Janine?
对  她还是你手下的时候
Yeah. When she worked for you.
只有在我知道她不对的时候
Only when I knew she was wrong.
她想写一篇阴谋论的报道
She's trying to draw up this whole conspiracy thing
涉及罗素  弗兰克・安德伍德
with Russo and Frank Underwood
还有造船厂关闭的事
and the whole shipyard closing.
我觉得是她错了
But I'm pretty sure she's wrong.
-觉得不代表确定  -不  我确定
- Pretty sure isn't the same as certain. - No. I am certain.
-你怎么知道  -我有联络人
- How do you know? - I have sources.
-安德伍德吗  -不是
- Underwood? - No.
算了  我再想想
No. Never mind. I'll figure it out.
-塔斯克太太  -叫我珍就好了
- Mrs. Tusk? - Jean, please.
你一定是弗兰克了  快请进
You must be Frank. Come in.
很高兴见到你
So nice to meet you.
客房在这边
The guest room is this way.
邀请我来住  真是太贴心了
It is very kind of you to have invited me to stay here.
我们这儿有舒适的床
Why waste the taxpayers' money on a hotel
何必浪费纳税人的钱住宾馆呢
when we have a perfectly good bed?
纳税人和我都十分感激
Well, both they and I are very grateful.
抱歉雷蒙德睡下了不能来迎你
I'm sorry Raymond isn't awake to greet you.
-他睡觉...  -我知道他习惯早起
- He goes to bed at... - I know he's an early riser.
我理解的
I understand.
你要我早上敲门叫你吗
Would you like a wake-up knock?
不用了  我手机上有闹铃
No. I have an alarm on my phone.
-晚安  -非常感谢
- Sleep tight. - Thank you so much.
我想问早安  但现在是大半夜
I would say good morning, but it's the middle of the night.
-见到你很高兴  -我也是
- It's a pleasure to meet you. - And you too.
我太吵了吗
Was I making too much noise?
不是  我闻到了培根香
No. I smelled bacon.
给你
Here.
咖啡还是酒
Coffee? Booze?
凌晨两点  任你选
2:00 a.m., you can go either way.
来杯水就好
Just water for now.
过滤过的水  你妻子会喜欢的
It's filtered. Your wife would approve.
你之前来过圣路易斯吗
You ever been to St. Louis before?
只来过机场
Just the airport.
你有什么看法
What do you think so far?
我只看到了你家一带
Well, I've only seen your neighborhood
还有州际公路沿途的风景
and whatever I could see out the window on the interstate.
可以了  看起来都差不多
Good enough. It's all pretty much the same.
抱歉
Excuse me.
喂
请等一等
我马上回来
听着  我还没洗澡
Listen, um, I still haven't showered.
还在想着中国的事
My mind is on China here.
不如你再睡一会儿
Uh, what do you say you get a few more zs
我们几小时后再好好谈
and we try this again in a few hours with our clothes on?
好啊
Sounds like a plan.
九点半在我办公室见
Meet me at my office at 9:30.
我派司机来接你
I'll have a driver pick you up.
能问下你为什么要那样做吗
Can I ask why you do that?
-做什么  -敲你的戒指
- Do what? - Tap your ring like that.
我在电视上见你那么做过
I've seen you do it on TV.
每次起身离桌或是结束演讲你都会那么做
Two taps every time you get up from a table or leave a lectern.
我父亲教我的
Something my father taught me.
可以强健指关节
It's meant to harden your knuckles
打架的时候就不会弄断它们
so you don't break them if you get into a fight.
而且还顺道敲了木头[西方的吉兆]
It also has the added benefit of knocking on wood.
我父亲认为成功
My father believed that success
准备和运气缺一不可
is a mixture of preparation and luck.
敲敲桌子可以一石二鸟
Tapping the table kills both birds with one stone.
你父亲不是个桃农吗
Your father was a peach farmer?
是的  而且做得并不好
Yes, he was. Not a very successful one.
-少了准备还是运气  -都少
- Lack of preparation or lack of luck? - Lack of both.
他说得好做不好
He was better at giving advice than following it.
喂
我看过你的报告了
这会给对方施加压力
小姐  小姐  你的卡
Miss? Miss, your card.
谢谢
Thank you.
盖拉格小姐  我是简宁・斯克斯基
Ms. Gallagher, my name's Janine Skorsky.
我是头条网的记者
I'm a reporter at Slugline.
-我写了关于议员的专访...  -我记得
- I wrote the profile on Congressman... - I remember.
-你有空吗  -如果这是关于彼得  我...
- Do you have a minute? - If this is about Peter, I...
不  是关于保罗・凯普拉
No. It's about Paul Capra.
我们知道他可能会接替罗素竞选议员
We know that he might be running for Congressman Russo's old seat.
我不能发表意见
I can't comment on that.
我们只是在调查去年四月
We're just trying to do some background
造船厂倒闭一事的背景
on the shipyard closing last April.
听着  我只想好好吃顿早饭
Listen, I just want to eat my breakfast.
我们得到消息称
We have sources that are saying
有人对议员施压
that the Congressman was being pressured by someone
让他不做抗争
to not fight the closure.
-谁  -我正在查
- Who? - That's what I'm trying to figure out.
我保证我们的谈话不会见报
This is completely off the record, I promise you.
-你好  克里斯蒂娜  -道格  你好
- Hi, Christina. - Doug, hi.
-你还好吗  -还好
- How you holding up? - I'm okay.
我很好
I'm... I'm good.
我看你坐在这儿  介不介意...
I saw you sitting over here. You mind if I...
不介意  请吧
No. Please.
斯克斯基女士  对吗
Ms. Skorsky, right?
你以前在《先驱报》时我们谈过几次
I believe we spoke a few times when you used to work at the Herald.
如果我能突破新闻处找到你
Whenever I could get past the press office gauntlet to you.
我们管理很严格
We do like to run a tight ship.
你为什么来国会大厦
So what brings you to the Capitol?
我只想问问盖拉格小姐
I was just asking Ms. Gallagher
谁在竞选填补宾州第一选区的议员一职
who's running to fill the vacant seat in Pennsylvania's 1st.
实话说  我们不知道
Well, the honest answer is we don't know.
谢谢你抽出时间  盖拉格小姐
Thank you for your time, Ms. Gallagher.
有谁来问你你不想回答的问题
Anyone starts harassing you with questions you don't want to answer,
就告诉我
you let me know.
我会处理
I'll handle them.
你要忙的事已经够多了
You got enough on your plate right now.
谢谢  道格  我很感激
Thanks, Doug. I appreciate that.
坚持住  好吗
Hang in there, okay?
行
Yes.
乌干达
Uganda,
秘鲁
Peru,
尼泊尔
Nepal,
印度尼西亚
Indonesia...
尼加拉瓜
Nicaragua.
你的旅行经历可真够丰富的
Well, you are quite the well traveled man.
不不  我是个居家的人
No. I'm the man who stays at home.
这些都是珍给我带回来的
Jean brought those back for me.
-塔斯克先生  我...  -叫名字就好
- Mr. Tusk, I am... - First names.
毕竟  我们一起吃过培根
After all, we have broken bacon together.
可以认为我们挺熟的了
We can safely assume that we're familiar.
雷蒙德  我知道你是个大忙人
Raymond, I realize that you are a very busy man,
那我就直切主题了
so I'm gonna cut right to the chase.
总统诚挚地希望
The President sincerely would like you
你能出任下届副总统
to become the next Vice President.
这个我已经知道了
That part I already knew.
我是来说服你同意的
And I'm here to convince you to say yes.
这我也知道
Another thing I already knew.
那就不知道
Well, I don't know that
我能不能告诉你什么新消息了
I can tell you anything you don't already know.
但也许你能告诉我  你的顾虑是什么
But perhaps you can tell me what your hesitation is.
请说
Speak.
行
Yes.
我理解  你有些顾忌
Now, I understand you might have some concerns
财务状况公开所导致的...
about the financial disclosures leading...
请说
Speak.
不行
No.
此时此刻  在六个时区有八个人
I have eight people representing me at eight
在八个同时召开的会议上代表我
simultaneous meetings in six time zones right now.
我就坐在这儿回答问题
I sit here and answer their questions,
但问题必须用简单的肯否定就能回答
provided they come in the form of a single yes or no proposition.
那么  让我试试
Well, then, let me give that a try.
你愿意担任副总统吗
Would you like to be the Vice President?
愿意还是不愿意
Yes or no?
稍等一会儿
Hold on a minute.
非常抱歉
I am very sorry.
给我二十分钟  了结这些会议
Let me have 20 minutes to wrap up these meetings.
然后我们离开办公室
And then what do you say we get out of the office
远离这该死的电话
and away from this damn phone?
去我车那里等我
Meet me at my car.
贝蒂会告诉你停车位置
Betty can tell you where it's parked.
说吧
Go ahead.
他在回避
He's deflecting.
我分辨不出是因为
What I can't tell is whether it's because
他想拒绝  还是想让我哄着他答应
he's inclined to say no or wants to be wooed to say yes.
不管怎样  我得慢慢引他说话
Either way, I'll have to ease him into the conversation,
不能太直白了
not be so blunt.
这趟行程恐怕会比预计要长
This trip may take longer than I thought.
我们已经找遍了所有的文件柜
We've looked through all the file cabinets.
他电脑里没记录吗
They're not on his computer?
议员手写的便条没有
Not with the Congressman's handwritten notes.
知道了  我去他办公室看看
All right. I'll check his office.
这片树林能给人慰藉
There is a comfort to these woods.
这儿就像我的后院
Like they're my backyard.
其实可以这么说  这块地是我的
Well, they are my backyard, in a way. I own them.
多少地
How much land?
六千英亩
Six thousand acres.
我这几天能去看看你的富顿电站吗
You think I could get a tour of your Fulton plant while I'm in town?
如果你想  但...
If you'd like. But...
我不懂你撇下这美景
I don't know why you'd want to be there
跑那儿去做什么
when you could be out here.
我从没见过核电站
I've never seen a nuclear plant.
没什么可看的
Not much to see.
钢筋混凝土  到处是蒸汽
Steel, concrete, a lot of steam.
总统并不是很支持核能
The President hasn't exactly been a big supporter of nuclear power.
那是你犹豫的原因吗
Is that, uh, part of your hesitation...
害怕政府...
that fear that the administration...
他只是圆润处事罢了
He's just being savvy.
日本核爆后核能很难让人接受
Nuclear energy is a tough sell after Japan.
但这又是目前唯一
But it's the only option we have right now
不会完全毁坏地球的能源
that doesn't completely trash the planet.
反对核能的观点都是感情用事
The argument against nuclear power is an emotional one.
你不凭感情做决定
And you don't make decisions based on emotion.
凭感情做的决定不叫决定
Decisions based on emotion aren't decisions at all.
那是直觉
They're instincts,
但也很有价值
which can be of value.
理性和非理性是互补的
The rational and the irrational complement each other.
分开就无力许多
Individually, they're far less powerful.
那你对副总统一职的考虑
And which category do your thoughts on the
是直觉还是决定呢
vice presidency fall into?
听到鸟叫声了吗
Do you hear that song?
是只隐居鸫
It's a hermit thrush.
看不见他
Can't see him.
孤独的鸫鸟
"Solitary, the thrush...
隐居起来  自我流放
"The hermit, withdrawn to himself,
离开居巢
"avoiding the settlements,
独自歌唱
"sings by himself a song."
-知道这首诗吗  -不知道
- Do you know the poem? - No, I don't.
沃尔特・惠特曼[美国诗人]的诗
It's Walt Whitman.
写亚伯拉罕・林肯之死的
It's about the death of Abraham Lincoln.
他就在那边
He's over there somewhere.
我当然知道那首破诗
Yes, I know the damn poem.
在桑蒂诺学过
We studied it at the Sentinel.
我问教授
I said to my Professor,
为什么要悼念总统或任何死去的人呢
"Why mourn the death of Presidents, or anyone for that matter?
死人又听不到
"The dead can't hear us."
而他问我是否信天堂
And he asked me if I believed in heaven.
我说不
I said no.
他又问我是否不信上帝
And then he asked if I had no faith in God.
我说  你错了
I said, "You have it wrong.
是上帝不信我们
"It's God who has no faith in us."
去树林深处吧
Deeper into the woods.
我觉得你太多疑了
I think you're being paranoid.
我一坐下他就来了  很诡异
He came up right after I sat down. It was creepy.
我跟你说  是乌麦克
I'm telling you, it was Womack.
安德伍德说的
Is that what Underwood said?
他没明说  但还能有谁
He didn't name names. But who else?
这怎么了  议员互做人情  很正常
What's the big deal? Congressmen trade favors.
其中一个自杀了
One of these congressmen committed suicide.
我觉得你在瞎想  简宁  想把...
I think you're stretching here, Janine. To try and connect...
我追过大鱼
I have gone after big fish before.
我知道被监视是什么感觉
I know what it feels like to be watched.
乌麦克当上多数党领袖三天
Underwood's education bill went to the floor
安德伍德的教育法案就进入投票
just three days after Womack became majority leader.
你泄露了教育法案的初稿
You leaked the education bill.
还有科恩的社论
And then there was the Kern article.
那是完全不同的两件事
Those were two completely different stories.
等等  那人是谁
Wait. What was the guy?
叫什么来着
Uh, what was his name?
爆料说科恩为校报写了那篇社论
He's the one who told that Kern wrote the article for the school paper.
-罗伊・科佩尼科  -你该去找他
- Roy Kapeniak. - You should go talk to him.
-这没联系  -你就是联系
- There's no link. - Except you.
安德伍德在利用你  佐伊
Underwood's been using you, Zoe.
你不想知道原因吗
Don't you want to know why?
雷米・丹顿在二号线
Remy Danton's on line two.
他说有要事
He says it's important.
-你好  雷米  -你好  克莱尔
- Hello, Remy. - Hey, Claire.
我刚接到桑科公关部的电话
I got a call from the P.R. Team at Sancorp.
说吉莉安・科尔不合作
They said Gillian Cole isn't being cooperative.
你是说她还没回复他们吗
Hasn't gotten back to them, you mean?
不  她直接说她不想让摄制组去
No. Told them point-blank she doesn't want the film crew there.
我在看她的邮件  她说
I'm looking at an e-mail. She wrote that
他们会破坏项目和当地社区
they would be disruptive to the project and local community.
那是她的还是你的意思
Is that her, or is that coming from you?
不  我明确说过  让她配合工作
No. I made it very clear that I wanted her to work with them.
看来她完全违背了你的要求
Well, it seems like she's doing the opposite.
我跟她谈谈
I will speak to her,
之后亲自向公关部解释
and then I'll sort things out with the P.R. Team personally.
-谢谢  克莱尔  -不客气
- Thank you, Claire. - You bet.
吉莉安去吃午饭了吗
Is Gillian at lunch?
她今天没来  身体不舒服
She didn't come in yet today. She's not feeling well.
她来了告诉我
Let me know when she gets here.
-你飞机几点的  -6点40
- What time is your flight? - 6:40.
那走吧  这会儿有点堵车
We should get going. There's gonna be traffic.
快好了
Almost ready.
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
你交往的那个老男人
The, uh, older man you were with.
是安德伍德吗
Was it Underwood?
那么你其实是想保住你自己
So, what this is really about is covering your own ass.
不对
That is not true.
你不想让人知道你和他上床
You don't want anybody to know you were sleeping with him.
这可不是客观报道  对吧
Not exactly objective reporting, is it?
不用你给我讲新闻伦理
Don't fucking lecture me on journalistic ethics.
你在《先驱报》时有多少新闻
How many of the stories you brought me at the herald
-是你通过...  -我不想谈这个
- were because you were... - I'm not gonna have this conversation.
好  那你自己打车去机场吧
Fine. Maybe you should take a cab to the airport.
别因为我坦诚而惩罚我
Don't punish me for being honest.
你不坦诚  是我问出来的
You haven't been honest. I had to ask.
而且你还没给我一个直接的回答
And you still haven't given me a straight answer.
是
Yes.
是他
It was him.
我不知道我能不能接受  佐伊
I... I don't know if I can do this, Zoe.
-什么意思  -你为了上位和议员上床
- Do what? - You fucked a Congressman to get ahead.
我不是第一个这么做的人  卢卡斯
I'm not the first person to ever do something like that, Lucas.
可是我没和别人上床  不是吗
But I'm not sleeping with those other people, am I?
那你现在恨我了
What, so you just hate me now?
不  我可能爱上你了
No. I probably love you.
这才是问题
That's the fucking problem.
走吧  我违章停车了
Let's go. I'm parked illegally.
我听说你们今天去林子里走了走
So I hear you went stomping through the woods today.
是的  然后雷蒙德还
We did, and then Raymond was kind enough
安排我去富顿电站参观
to arrange a tour of the Fulton plant.
我敢肯定你在想
And I'm sure you were wondering,
这个老东西什么时候才能说正事
"When is this old fool gonna get around to brass tacks?"
我来就是为了回答问题
I'm here to simply answer questions.
我想等你准备好了  自会做决定
I figured that you would make up your mind when you're ready.
这里有两个人
There are two minds here.
我们非常了解保密委托
We know all about the blind trust.
有什么让你们担心的吗
Does it concern either of you?
保密和委托
The words "Blind" And "Trust"
绝非我最喜欢的英语单词
are not among my favorites in the English language.
但理论上  我并不反对
But I have no problem with it in theory.
几年内不必管理我们的资产
Not managing our assets for a few years
确实可以减轻我们许多压力
could unburden us from a great deal of stress.
那还有什么不情愿的地方
Well, then, what does your reluctance stem from?
你觉得总统为什么要找我
Why do you think the President wants me?
我不能代表他说话  但如果我要...
Well, I can't speak on his behalf, but if I were to...
你来不就是为了代表他说话吗
Aren't you here to do just that... speak on his behalf?
如果让我推测  我认为总统...
If I were to speculate, I think the President would prob...
推测可不是一种好的投资方式
Speculation is a poor form of investment
同样也不是一种好的政治手段
and an equally poor form of politics.
把你知道的告诉我们
Tell me what you know.
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what you mean.
你觉得我应该怎么做
Well, what do you think I should do?
作为你个人  弗兰克・安德伍德
You, personally, Frank Underwood?
我的意见并不重要
My opinion isn't what matters here.
对我来说很重要  我应该去吗  去还是不去
It does to me. Should I do it? Yes or no?
需要考虑很多事情
Well, there's a great number of things to consider...
我肯定你都已经考虑过了
And I'm sure you've considered them all.
去还是不去  弗兰克
Yes or no, Frank?
不  我不会回答这个问题
No, I will not answer that question.
因为你觉得我不该去
Because you think I shouldn't.
因为我的想法不重要
Because it's not relevant.
那好  我换个方式问你
All right, then. Let me ask you another way.
你会接受这份工作吗
Would you take the job?
总统没找我
It hasn't been offered to me.
如果找了呢
What if it were?
我讨厌假设
I have a distaste for hypotheticals
就像你讨厌推测一样
just the same as you have a distaste for speculation.
好  好吧
All right, all right.
公事到此为止  我们可以明天继续谈
That's enough business for now. We can discuss it more tomorrow.
进来  进来  布鲁斯
Get in. Get in there, Bruce.
抱歉  抱歉打扰你了  女士
Sorry. Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
我找罗伊・科佩尼科
Um, I'm looking for Roy Kapeniak.
我以为他的拖车在那边  我找对地方了吗
I thought his trailer was over here. Am I in the right place?
一个月前的话你就找对地方了
You're in the right place a month ago.
他被赶走了
He got evicted.
总是在院子里打枪
He was shootin' off his gun too much in the yard.
你知道我该去哪找他吗
Do you know where I can find him?
找他干什么
Why?
我是他的亲戚  他的侄女
I'm a relative. His... his niece.
据我所知是出城了
Skipped town is what I heard.
有个姑娘和他一起生活  也许她知道
Had a girl livin' with him. Maybe she knows.
-叫艾柯  -艾柯
- Name was Echo. - Echo?
她自己这么说
That's what she went by, at least.
在40号公路那边的脱衣舞俱乐部工作
Works at the titty bar over on 40.
40号高速公路
Highway 40?
-过了汉堡王就是  -好的  谢谢
- Across from the Burger King. - Okay. Thank you.
21岁以下禁止入内  请出示身份证件  违法者将被起诉
姑娘免费进
Girls get in free.
-我找艾柯  -谁
- I'm looking for Echo. - Who?
艾柯
Echo.
罗伊是个疯子
Roy was a fucking wacko.
我和他同居真是蠢死了
I was stupid to live with him as long as I did.
-你知道他现在在哪吗  -不知道也不在乎
- Do you know where he is now? - I don't know, and I don't care.
他有没有说过我写的那篇报道
He ever talk about the article I wrote?
整天唠叨  还裱起来了
All the time. He had it framed.
应该还在拖车里
Bet it's still in the trailer
如果那车没进废车场的话
if it's not in a junkyard right now.
他说过为什么打电话给我吗
Did he say why he called me?
-跟你说过吗  -我当时在场
- Did he ever tell you? - I was there.
-什么意思  -那人来的时候
- Where? - When the guy showed up.
谁
Who?
我不会写你的名字
I won't name names.
别管罗伊・科佩尼科了
Fuck Roy Kapeniak.
你又不欠他什么
You don't owe him shit.
那人说他是个议员
Some guy who said he was a Congressman.
是...
Was it...
他吗
him?
不是
No.
那人要年轻一点  高一点
He was younger, tall,
头发很少  长得不错
not much hair, pretty good-looking.
-对  就是他  -你肯定
- Yeah, that was him. - You're absolutely sure?
他带了波旁酒  毒品  待了一晚上
He brought bourbon, blow, stayed the whole night.
整件事都是他的主意
The whole thing was his idea.
说那篇社论是科恩写的
What, to say that Kern wrote the editorial?
那人什么都没做  都是罗伊写的
That guy didn't write anything. It was all Roy.
好的  我知道我说过不会写你的名字
Okay, look, I know I said that I wouldn't name names,
如果你坚持我是不会写
and I won't if that's what you want.
但你可以因此一夜成名
But you could be famous overnight.
脱口秀  电视  全国...
Talk shows, TV, the whole country...
想都别想
No way.
你不用再跳舞了
You wouldn't have to dance anymore.
你想干什么都行
You could do whatever you want.
别他妈写我名字  好吗
Don't use my fucking name, okay?
我都说了不该说的了
I already said more than I should have.
-斯坦普  都半夜了  -两件事  先生
- Stamper, it's midnight. - Two things, boss.
第一件  简宁・斯克斯基
First, Janine Skorsky
今早去找了克里斯蒂娜
ambushed Christina this morning.
在她能提更多问题前被我拦下了
I intercepted her before she could ask too much.
-要担心吗  -我能控制住  先生
- Should we be worried? - I can keep this contained, sir.
只是告诉你一声
I just wanted you to know.
好的  还有件事呢
All right. What's the other thing?
道尔的调查做完了
Doyle came back with his research.
我刚发你邮箱了
I just e-mailed it to you.
总统跟你说他不认识塔斯克  对吗
The President told you he and Tusk didn't know each other, right?
是的  他说他们只见过一面
Yeah. He said they met once, I think,
在一个募捐会上
at a fund-raiser.
看来他说谎了
That would appear to be a lie.
好的  我打开邮件了
All right. I have it in front of me now.
道尔列出了他能查到的
Doyle catalogued all the instances he could find
他们俩同时出现在同一城市的情况
in which the two of them were in the same city at the same time.
红色项是他们共同出席的活动
Items in red are events that they both attended.
他还查到了别的
And he found something else.
沃克之前做私营生意的时候
Back in Walker's private sector days,
他曾是先锋航空公司的执行总裁
he was the C.E.O. of Pioneer Airlines.
公司被卖给美联航时
Guess who owned a third of the stock
猜猜谁拥有三分之一的股份
when it was sold to united?
雷蒙德・塔斯克
Raymond Tusk.
我猜他和沃克相当熟
My guess is that he and Walker know each other quite well.
好的  我再看下邮件  回头打给你
All right. Let me look this over. I'll call you back.
我被耍了
I'm being played.
为什么
But why?
在台湾
有什么样的投资
-我又把你吵醒了  -没有
- Did I wake you again? - No.
我想谈谈
I'd like to talk.
稍等一下
Give me a moment.
我刚刚说
我要知道
现在那里
好了  就这样
卡罗莱纳长尾鹦鹉
Carolina Parakeet.
不对  但很接近了
You're wrong, but you're close.
这是太阳锥尾鹦鹉
This is the Sun Conure.
看起来很相似
They look very similar,
但卡罗莱纳长尾鹦鹉已经灭绝了
but the Carolina Parakeet is extinct.
被认为有害  所以被杀尽了
Was killed off because it was considered a pest.
却是个很有趣的物种
Interesting species, though.
贪食
Voracious appetite.
还有毒  猫吃了它会死
And he was poison. Cats who ate him died.
你来圣路易斯后
This bird is not the only thing
认错的可不只有这只鸟
you've misidentified since you've been in St. Louis.
你和沃克是老朋友了
You and Walker are old friends.
他不是让我来审查你的
I wasn't sent here to vet you.
很好
Very good.
那告诉我来的原因
Tell me why I am here, then.
我好审查你
So I can vet you.
为副总统的职位吗
For the vice presidency?
总统很看重我的意见  而且一般会照做
The President values my advice, and he tends to follow it.
比如我建议他不要让你当国务卿那次
Like when I advised him not to make you Secretary of State.
那建议很糟糕
That was very bad advice.
是的
Yes, it was.
是我犯下的最大错误之一
One of the larger mistakes I've made,
而我几乎不犯错
and I very rarely make mistakes of any size.
你真是个相当难搞的人物
You've proven yourself to be quite difficult.
科恩  教师罢工  现在是马修斯
Kern, the teachers' strike, now Matthews.
你觉得这都是我干的
You attribute all that to me?
如果要我猜的话
If I had to guess.
一位智者曾对我说
A smart man once said to me
推测不是一种好的政治手段
that speculation is a poor form of politics.
你还是说你知道的事吧  雷蒙德
Why don't you stick to what you know, Raymond?
我知道  如果你打定了主意
What I know is you are extremely effective
会非常有成效
at what you set your mind to.
这对我很有价值
That is valuable to me,
我也跟加勒特说  这对他可能也很有价值
and I've already told Garrett that it could be valuable to him...
选个同时涉足行政部门和立法部门
somebody at his side with one foot in the executive branch
又支持他的人
and one in the legislative.
他很愿意考虑
He is very open to the idea.
该我推测了
My turn to speculate.
你的推荐
Your recommendation...
是有代价的
comes at a price.
事实
Fact.
我有你想要的东西
I have something that you want.
你有我想要的东西
You have something that I want.
我说什么可笑的话了吗
Have I said something amusing?
只是我曾太多次跟别人说过这种话
Oh, I've just sat too many times on your side of the table
不禁觉得自己会听到这种话无比的讽刺
not to enjoy the irony of finding myself on this side of it.
你想听听我想要什么吗
Would you like to hear what I want?
我不把自己绑在我不认识的人身上
I don't shackle myself to people I don't know.
我想让你帮个忙
What I want is one favor.
只有这一个要求
One and only one.
什么忙
Which is?
我要确定你会答应
I need to be certain you'll grant it
才能说得更细
before I'll take the risk of being more specific.
一张空头支票
A blank check.
差不多
Of sorts.
你不会给任何人开空头支票
You would never grant anyone a blank check.
不  但面临抉择的不是我
No. But I'm not sitting on that side of the table.
在我们那地方  还相信握手为诺
We still believe in handshakes where I come from.
华盛顿的人还相信吗
Do they still mean anything in Washington?
-你给谁打电话  -叫出租车载我去机场
- Who are you calling? - Car service to get me to the airport.
弗兰克
Frank,
我会告诉总统我要仔细考虑
I will tell the President that I want until Friday
到周五才能给出我的建议
to think things over before I make my recommendation.
改主意的话告诉我
Let me know if you change your mind.
我给你安排车吧
And let me arrange the car for you.
你好  我想叫一辆车  谢谢
Hi. I'd like to arrange a car, please.
-你感觉怎么样  -比昨天好些
- How are you feeling? - Better than yesterday.
如果又恶心了  可能还得提前走
But I might take off early if, uh, the nausea comes back.
你赶走了桑科公司的人
I find it interesting that you stay home
第二天就待在了家里  这很有趣
the day after you blow off the sancorp people.
你不是觉得难受  吉莉安
You weren't feeling sick, Gillian.
我觉得你指责我
I find it extremely offensive
用怀孕作为逃避的理由很无礼
that you'd accuse me of hiding behind my pregnancy.
你很清楚我的意思
You knew what I wanted.
博茨瓦纳项目是我的
The Botswana project is mine.
在我的保护下  用我筹集的钱
Under my umbrella, using money I raised.
你答应给我自主权
You promised me autonomy.
让我们单独待会儿  谢谢
Um, excuse us for a moment, please.
我答应给你权力
I promised to empower you.
这和你不问我
That's not the same thing
就自作主张是两码事
as you doing  as you choose without consulting me.
我不会让一个我投入了三年心血
I'm not gonna allow a project I've put almost three years
-的项目  -如果没有桑科
- of my life into... - your project wouldn't be happening
你的项目根本不可能实现
if it weren't for sancorp.
我没要他们帮忙
I didn't ask for their help.
你达成协议之前怎么不和我商量
How about consulting me before you struck a deal?
我们把话说清楚
Let's get something very clear.
我运营这个组织  你为它工作
I run the organization. You work for it.
我们的协议是联盟  克莱尔
Our agreement is an affiliation, Claire.
-世界之井不是你的下人  -是  它就是
- Worldwell isn't your vassal. - Yes, it is, entirely,
如果非要直说的话
if we're going to be blunt about it.
这不是你六个月前的提议
That's not what you proposed six months ago.
你签合同的时候就等于接受了这一切
It's what you signed up for when you signed the contract.
我们的协议有一份诚意...
There was a good faith understanding that...
你对我的违抗  让我失去了这份诚意
And you dissolved that good faith by disobeying me.
-违抗你  -是的
- Disobeying you? - Yes.
我威胁到你了  是吧
I threaten you, don't I?
你没有什么能威胁到我
Nothing about you threatens me.
也许你应该去休假
But maybe you should take a leave of absence.
你要开除我
Are you firing me?
这取决于你  但现在你得离开
That's up to you, but right now you should leave.
她愿意公开吗
Did you get her on record?
不  否则她就不和我说话了
No. She wouldn't talk to me otherwise.
我们需要确凿证据证明安德伍德是幕后黑手
We need hard proof that Underwood was behind it.
这事让我很紧张
This whole thing is making me really nervous.
害怕你会暴露
That you'll be exposed?
不是
Not that.
那可是弗兰西斯
It's Francis.
如果这事真像我们想的那么大
If this really goes as deep as we think,
他已经在监视你
and he's already watching you...
-你认为他很危险  -我知道他很危险
- You think he's dangerous? - I know he is.
所以我们必须得查下去
Then that's why we have to keep going.
他能毁掉一个人
He crushes people...
-你好  卡拉姆  -你好
- Hey, Callum. - Hey.
如果你不怕  就不会做这份工作了
Look, if you weren't afraid, you wouldn't be doing your job.
我写过的唯一一篇
The only articles that I have ever written
真正重要的文章简直把我吓坏了
that truly mattered scared the shit out of me.
我们得了解关于罗素的一切
We need to know about anything that might've happened with Russo.
安德伍德用来威胁他的事
Something Underwood could have held over him.
咱们得再去找克里斯蒂娜・盖拉格
We have to go back to Christina Gallagher,
看她能说点什么
see if she'll give us something.
我不能去了  如果我又去找
It can't be me. If I go back for a second time...
我去吧
I'll do it.
你完全不知道总统和塔斯克关系很亲密吗
You honestly had no idea that the President and Tusk were close?
从我们开始竞选到上任这段时间内
He never showed up once on any call sheet,
他从没出现在任何通告单
phone log or schedule during
通话记录或者日程表上
the campaign or since we've been in office.
我很想相信你  琳达
I'd love to believe you, Linda,
但这很困难
but I'm finding it very difficult.
我把你蒙在鼓里有什么好处呢
What would I gain by keeping you in the dark?
我跟你一样震惊  弗兰克
I am as shocked as you are, Frank.
别让他看出来你知道了
Well, don't let on that you know.
-当然  -总统说什么
- Of course not. - What's the President saying?
他周二想见你  让你报告塔斯克的事
He wants to meet with you Tuesday to get your report on Tusk.
真是胡闹
That's a farce.
要我找点理由推迟会面吗
Should I come up with a reason to delay the meeting?
不用了  或许能打探出点什么
No. Maybe we'll learn something.
-什么时候  -下午两点
- What time? - 2:00 P.M.
好吧  我会去的  谢谢你  琳达
All right. I'll be there. Thank you, Linda.
-我们有一礼拜时间  -做什么
- We have one week. - To accomplish what exactly?
逼迫塔斯克  他想让我感激他  休想
To force Tusk's hand. He wants me beholden to him? No.
我们得让他来找我
We have to make him come crawling to me.
他的弱点是什么
What's his weakness?
他的财产
His fortune.
那不是他的优势吗
Wouldn't you say that's his strength?
一旦流失就不是了
Not if it's slipping away.
-怎么在一夜之间搞掉四百亿  -做不到
- How do you make 40 billion disappear overnight? - We can't.
但可以制造出他的财产有危险的假象
But maybe we can create the illusion that it's in danger.
你给我的那份他的资产报告
The brief you gave me on his assets.
他的总资产净值有多少
How much of his total net worth is...
是核能方面的
in nuclear power?
大概是三分之一
About a third.
美国有16个反应堆  全球37个
Sixteen reactors here in the states, 37 worldwide.
那就是我们打击他的武器
Well, that's what we hit him with.
我们要打击他的核利益
We go after his nuclear interests.
即便如此
Even so,
他的其他投资价值250亿美金
he's got 25 billion in other investments.
道格  他白手起家
Doug, this is a man who built his fortune from nothing.
钱对他毫无意义
The money doesn't mean anything to him.
重在钱所代表的东西
It's what it represents.
-是什么  -他一生的努力
- Which is what? - His life's work.
接通雷米・丹顿的电话
Get Remy Danton on the phone.
尽快安排一个会面
Set up a meeting as quickly as you can.
知道了
You got it.
塔斯克理解权力和金钱之间的区别
Tusk understands the difference between power and money.
因此他是个危险人物
That's precisely what makes him dangerous.
他衡量财富的标准不是私人飞机
He doesn't measure his wealth in private jets
而是拉拢的人心
but purchased souls.
我做了这么多努力  如今目标近在咫尺
I've worked too hard to get within arm's reach of the prize
绝不能在即将到手时被砍断双手
only to have my hand cut off just before I seize it.
佐伊・巴恩斯  来见克里斯蒂娜・盖拉格
Zoe Barnes, here to see Christina Gallagher.
抱歉  我没看到有预约
I'm sorry. I don't see an appointment.
肯定搞错了  我预约了11点半的
Oh, there must be a mistake. I have an 11:30.
稍等一下
One second.
我叫佐伊・巴恩斯
My name is Zoe Barnes.
我在头条网工作
I work at Slugline.
你跟我同事简宁・斯克斯基谈过了
You spoke to my colleague Janine Skorsky.
-小姐  -没事  谢谢
- Miss... - Oh, we're fine, thanks.
你不能这么闯进来
You can't just come in here...
很多关于彼得的事你都不知道
There are things you don't know about Peter.
关于罗伊・科佩尼科的文章是我写的
I wrote the article about Roy Kapeniak.
请快走吧  马上
Please leave. Right now.
是彼得说服他跟我谈的
It was Peter who convinced him to talk to me.
什么  我不  不明白
What? I don't... I don't understand.
-他为什么  -有人强迫他做的
- Why would he... - Somebody pressured him to do it.
1月24号晚上
The night of January 24th.
他去找科佩尼科
That's when he went to speak to Kapeniak.
你记得就职典礼左右
Do you remember anything strange
发生过什么奇怪的事吗
around the time of the inauguration?
-任何可能成为把柄的事  -没有
- Anything that could have been held over him? - No, I don't.
如果他被牵连进了
If he was mixed up in things
最终导致他自杀的事情
that in any way contributed to his suicide,
你不想知道吗
wouldn't you want to know?
我没想火上浇油
I'm not trying to cause you any more pain.
我只想要真相
I just want the truth.
而你比任何人都应该知道
And you deserve that more than anyone.
-你刚说什么时候  -1月24日
- What was the date? - The 24th of January.
■
Blind Trust
美国富翁出任公职后
会把自己的股票基金等交给财务公司打理
对财务公司的操作和决策全不知情
避免工作和私人利益有牵涉
翻译  小蟹
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  waterlike
翻译  某豚
翻译  某羽
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  天意
翻译  小饭
翻译  sakura
时间轴  吉吉
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第十二集
人人影视倾情奉献